

Adaptable and personable Management & Sales Professional with 9 years' collective experience in staff training, stakeholder engagement, and quality assurance. Proficient in troubleshooting, customer relationship management, and people's operation. Excel at conflict resolution, process improvement, and interpersonal communication.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### L'OCCITANE - SAN FRANCISCO CENTRE, CA - DEC 2022 - JAN 2024

#### Sales Associate

- Provided exceptional customer service to drive repeat business and customer satisfaction. Often met or exceeded sales goals during holidays season or special events.
- · Mastered internal salesforce portal to maintain customer relationships and interests.
- Performed various diverse tasks: staging sales floor changes, bank runs, technical and customer support.

### GOOGLE VIA ADECCO - MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA - 2020 - 2022

### **Staffing Operation Supervisor**

- Led a team of 35+ contracted Recruiting Coordinators through virtual and returning to office by establishing constructive core team values, encouraging knowledge sharing, and prioritizing a "people-first" approach.
- Boosted team metrics by 126% during unpredictable hiring volumes by developing training modules, hosting office hours, and resolving stakeholder escalations with high-touch, solution-based support.
- Supported hiring initiatives like "One Day Offer" in India, and hosted 50+ Virtual Meet & Greets for director-level candidates.
- Co-creating a globally scalable supervisor dashboard, streamlining team metric assessment.

## **Recruiting Coordinator**

- Mastered google's internal ATS system and provided technical support to teammates. Created and conducted onboarding training for 30+ new hires and 50+ cross-regional partners during an internal re-org.
- Managed 10+ business-critical requests per week while managing calendars across multiple timezones.
- Exceeded quantity and quality metrics by 110% consistently through attention to details and timely follow-ups.

#### FREELANCE PHOTOGRAPHER — 2014 - 2020

- Captured professional headshots and documented corporate / school events, engagements, and weddings.
- Coordinated, managed, and adapted event timelines according to clients' needs.

# ARTIST YEAR (FELLOWSHIP) — PHILADELPHIA, PA — 2016-2017

- Served as a teaching artist for 7th & 8th grade students at a Philadelphia Mastery Charter School. Instructed students in photography fundamentals, editing, and publishing as an elective course.
- Created proposal and acquired 4 professional DSLRs for student hands-on experiences in class, school events, and personal use.
- Organized the creation of digital online portfolios and a yearbook project per student interest

# **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- $\cdot \, \text{Stakeholder Engagement} \cdot \text{Relationship Management} \cdot \, \text{Training \& Development} \cdot \, \text{CRM \& ATS Systems} \cdot \, \text{Sales} \cdot \, \text{$
- · Quality Assurance · Technical Troubleshooting · Digital Editing · Business Administration · JavaScript ·

### **LANGUAGE & LINKS**

Fluent in Cantonese, semi-fluent in Mandarin · Ability to read/dictate in simplified and traditional Chinese <a href="https://draconmarius.github.io/react-cv/">https://draconmarius.github.io/react-cv/</a>
<a href="https://wix.com/marikma/portfolio/">https://wix.com/marikma/portfolio/</a>

#### **EDUCATION**

Drexel University — Bachelor of Science in Entertainment and Arts Management Extension - UC Berkeley — Full Stack Coding Bootcamp